Guide to the Rice University Assistant to the President papers: Carl MacDowell, 1963-2001 (bulk 1990-1998) UA 084
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: On Campus - General, 1963 – 2000
  The material in this series is subdivided alphabetically, by title, into administrative offices. The folders within each heading were then also filed in alphabetical order. Original order was maintained so there may be overlapping of dates on some folders. One box of cassettes was added at the end of Provost Section. One box of legal size (oversize) material is at the end of the VP for Finance and Administration. The material in the section named "Committees – Meeting Binders" may have come from Neal Lane, Provost. The material was removed from the binders and included in this section of the President's Office records. The documents are filed the way they were in the binder – by date and then by Committee name. There are some folders relating to the Task Force on Institutional Policy Review that are marked DESTROY IN 2005 under the President's Section, Box 81.
  - Admissions
    - Admissions, 1989, 1993, 1995-97 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Admissions, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Admissions, 1995-96 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Admissions, 1994, 1996-97 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Admissions, 1997-98 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Admissions, 1997-98 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - McGuire Associates-Admission Review, 1995-96 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - McGuire Associates – Reports on Enrollment Mgt., 1996 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Special Admits, 1996-98 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Survey, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - (Special) Accounting, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Admission of Student Athletes, 1991-94 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Admission of Student Athletes, 1995-96 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Admission of Student Athletes, Revision, 1991-94 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Athletics
    - Anderson Audit, 1986-92 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - (Rice) Arena, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Athletic Alternatives, 1983, 1987-89 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Athletic Alternatives, 1988-92 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Athletic Alternatives, 1992-94 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Athletic Conference Move, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Athletic Review Committee 1990-91 (Folder 1) (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Athletic Review Committee, 1990-91 (Folder 2) (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Athletic Review Committee, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Athletic Review Committee Evaluations, 1992-93 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Athletic Review Committee Report, 1992 (Folder 1) (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Athletic Review Committee Report, 1992 (Folder 2) (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Athletic Steering Committee, 1994, 1996-97 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Athletic Steering Committee, 1997-98 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Athletics, 1985, 1988-1992 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Athletics, 1991-92 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Athletics, 1989-92 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Athletics, 1991-92 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Athletics, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Athletics, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Athletics, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Athletics, 1988-89, 1992-94 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Athletics, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Athletics, 1995-96 (Folder 1) (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Athletics, 1996 (Folder 2) (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Athletics, 1996-97 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Athletics, 1996-97 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Athletics, 1996-97 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Athletics, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Athletics, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Athletics, 1996-98 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Athletics, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Athletics, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Athletics, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Business Practices Review, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Concerts, 1996-97 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Concerts/Billy Joel-Elton John, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Concerts/Strait, George, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Concerts/Witt, Marcos, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Drug Testing, 1987-88 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - (John L. Cox) Fitness Center, 1994-96 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - For Rice's Honor, 1995-96 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Gender Equity, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - McMinn, Bill Visit, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Mellon Athletics Study, 1994-95 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Outside Income Agreement, 1997-98 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Practice Facility, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Public Opinion, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Rice Stadium, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Rice Stadium, 1994-96 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Rice Stadium, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Rice Stadium/Proposal for Security, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Rice Stadium/Turf Conversion, 1994-96 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Scheduling of Events During Exam Period, 1987-89 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Southwest Conference Blowup, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Sports/Baseball, 1995-96 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Sports/Baseball, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Sports/Basketball, 1995-97 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Sports/Basketball, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Sports/Football, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Sports/Football, 1995-96 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Sports/Football, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Sports/Football, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Sports/Swimming, 1998-99 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Title IX, 1993-94 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - U. S. Soccer Federation, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Committees
    - Academic Affairs, March 19, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Academic Affairs, May 10, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Academic Affairs, September 30, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Academic Affairs, November 18, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Academic Affairs, March 16, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Academic Affairs, May 10, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Academic Affairs, October 13, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Academic Affairs, October 13, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Academic Affairs, December 8, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Academic Affairs, 1995-96 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Academic Affairs/Leaves of Absence and Sabbaticals, 1993-94 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Ad Hoc Curriculum Review, 1996-99 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Ad Hoc Dismissal, 1996-97 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Ad Hoc, General, 1989, 1994, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Ad Hoc on Access, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Ad Hoc on Distribution Courses, 1984, 1988-89 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Ad Hoc on Environment, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Ad Hoc on Environment, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Ad Hoc on Faculty Retirement, 1995, 1997-98 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Ad Hoc on Faculty Retirement /Report, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Ad Hoc on International Education, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Ad Hoc on Judicial Affairs, 1995-96 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Ad Hoc on Martin Luther King Day, 1992-93 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Ad Hoc on Outreach, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Ad Hoc on Sexual Harassment, 1995, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Admissions, 1983-89 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Admissions, 1993-97 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Affirmative Action, 1983, 1990-91, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Affirmative Action, 1995-98 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Athletics, 1984-89 (Folder 1) (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Athletics, 1984-89 (Folder 2) (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Athletics, 1990-92 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Athletics, 1993-94 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Athletics, 1994-96 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Athletics, 1992, 1997-98 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Benefits, 1997-98 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Campus Store, 1977, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - College Masters, 1979, 1984-88 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - College Masters, 1994, 1996-98 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Commission on Women, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Community Affairs, 1985-89 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Community Affairs, 1992-94 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Computers, 1982-85, 1987-88, 1990, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Environment Health and Safety, 1985, 1987-88, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Examinations and Standing, 1988-91 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Examinations and Standing, 1992-94 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Examinations and Standing, 1995-99 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Handbook Draft, Appointments and Promotions, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Council, 1986-92 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Council, 1993-94 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Council, 1995-96 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Council, 1997-99 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Council/Bylaws, 1987-88, 1995, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Council/Spousal Hiring Subcommittee, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Council/Elections, 1989-93 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Council/Elections, 1994-95 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1982/83 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1983/84 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1984/85 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1985/86 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1986/87 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1987/88 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1988/89 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1989/90 (Folder 1) (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1989/90 (Folder 2) (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1990/91 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1991/92 (computer disc) (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1992/93 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1994/95 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1995/96 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Fringe Benefits, 1982-89 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Fringe Benefits, 1990-93 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Fringe Benefits, 1995-97 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Graduate Council, 1982, 1984-89, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Graduate Council, 1996-98 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Honor Council, 1992, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Institutional Animal Care and Use, 1989, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - International Education, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - KTRU, 1996-97 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - KTRU, 1997-99 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Library, 1983-1992 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Library, 1993, 1995, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Marshal's, 1983-84, 1986-87, 1993, 1997-98 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Parking, 1995-98 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Promotion and Tenure, 1994-97 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Promotion and Tenure/Charts, 1993-94 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Public Lectures, 1982-88 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Public Lectures, 1993-98 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Purchasing and Receiving, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Religious Activity, 1987, 1993-95 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Research Council, 1983, 1985-87, 1989-94 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Residential Colleges Management Advisory, 1982, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Safety, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Salary Equity, 1989-92 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Salary Equity, 1989-92 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Scholarships and Awards, 1984, 1986-88, 1990, 1995-96 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Space Assignment, 1983, 1985-86, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Staff Advisory, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Standing, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Standing, 1984-85 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Standing, 1987-88 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Standing, 1987-88 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Standing, 1988-89 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Standing, 1988-89 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Standing, 1989-90 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Standing, 1990-91 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Standing, 1991-92 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Standing, 1992-93 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Standing, 1992-93 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Standing, 1994-95 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Standing, 1995-96 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Standing/Assignments, 1986-91 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Standing/SAC, GSA, and Alumni Recommendations, 1993-96 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Student Affairs, 1983, n. d. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Student Financial Aid, 1985-86 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Student Health, 1983-89, 1993-94 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Teaching, 1994-97 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Undergraduate Curriculum, 1982-84, 1987-92 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Undergraduate Curriculum, 1993-97 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Undergraduate Teaching, 1982-89, n. d. (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Undergraduate Teaching, 1990-93, n. d. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - University Council, 1985-89 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - University Council, 1990, 1993-94 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - University Council, 1995-96 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - University Council, 1996-98 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - University Council, 1994, 1997-98 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - University Council/Promotions and Tenure, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - University Council/Promotions and Tenure, 1988-90 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - University Council/Tenured Members, 1982-89 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - University Review Board, 1983-84, 1987-89, 1991, 1993, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Committees - Meetings Binders (Neal Lane)
    - Faculty Meetings, Faculty Council, Staff Meetings, University Council, 1986-87 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Meetings, Faculty Council, University Council, Staff Meetings, 1987-88 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Meetings, Faculty Council, Staff Meetings, University Council, Examinations and Standing Committee, 1988-89 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Meetings, Faculty Council, 1989-90 (Folder 1) (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - University Council, Staff Meetings, Examinations and Standing Committee, 1989-90 (Folder 2) (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Meetings, Faculty Council, 1990-91 (Folder 1) (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - University Council, Staff Meetings, Examinations and Standing Committee, 1990-91 (Folder 2) (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Meetings, Faculty Council, 1991-92 (Folder 1) (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - University Council, Staff Meetings, Examinations and Standing Committee, 1991-92 (Folder 2) (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Meetings, Faculty Council, University Council, 1992-93 (Folder 1) (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Staff Meetings, Examinations and Standing Committee, 1992-93 (Folder 2) (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Council, Faculty Meetings, University Council, Staff Meetings, 1993-94 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Council, Faculty Meetings, University Council, Staff Meetings, 1993-94 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Deans
    - Architecture, 1991-92 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Architecture, 1992-93 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Architecture, 1993-94 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Architecture, 1993-94 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Architecture, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Architecture, 1996-97 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Architecture, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Architecture, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Architecture/Advisory Council, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Architecture/Farokhi, Sohela Working Papers, 1994, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Architecture/Memorial for Paul Kennon, 1990-93 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Architecture/Preceptorship, 1991-92 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Architecture/Preceptorship, 1993-94 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Architecture/Rice Design Alliance, 1990-92 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Architecture/Rice Design Alliance, 1993-95 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Architecture/Rice Design Alliance, 1995-97 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Continuing Studies, 1991-92 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Continuing Studies, 1991-93 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Continuing Studies, 1993-94 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Continuing Studies, 1995-97 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Continuing Studies, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Continuing Studies/Review, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Continuing Studies/Berlin Wall, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Dean's Council, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Dean's Council, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Dean's Council, 1996-98 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Dean's Council/Agenda, 1993-94 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Engineering, 1991-92 (Folder 1) (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Engineering, 1991-92 (Folder 2) (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Engineering, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Engineering, 1994-95 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Engineering, 1994-95 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Engineering, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Engineering, 1996-97 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Engineering, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Engineering, 1998-99 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Engineering/Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology, 1988, 1991, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Engineering/Advisory Council, 1991-92 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Engineering/Advisory Council, 1993-94 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Engineering/Advisory Council, 1995-98 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Engineering/(The) Posse Foundation, Inc., 1993-95, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Engineering/Ryon Lab, 1996-97 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Engineering/Search Committee, 1997-98 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Humanities, 1989-92 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Humanities, 1992-93 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Humanities, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Humanities, 1994-95 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Humanities, 1996-97 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Humanities, 1996-97 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Humanities, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Humanities/Brown, Judith C., 1995, 1997-98 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Humanities/Humanities Building, 1997-98 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Humanities/Chile Program, 1988-90 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Humanities/Chile Program, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Humanities/Cross Cultural Studies Center, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Humanities/Dickens Project, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Humanities/(George R. Brown) Forensic Society, 1990-92 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Humanities/(George R. Brown) Forensic Society, 1991-93 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Humanities/Foundation Courses, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Humanities/Search, 1994-95 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Jones School, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Jones School, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Jones School, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Jones School, 1994-96 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Jones School, 1996 (Folder 1) (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Jones School, 1996 (Folder 2) (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Jones School, 1997-98 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Jones School, 1997-98 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Jones School, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Jones School/Annual Report-Expansion, 1993-94 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Jones School/Brown Foundation Investment Fund, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Jones School/Council of Overseers, 1993-98 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Jones School/Review of, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Jones School/Review of, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Jones School/Search, 1996-97 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Jones School/Steering Committee, 1996-97 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994-97 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Natural Sciences, 1991-94 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Natural Sciences, 1990-93 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Natural Sciences, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Natural Sciences, 1994-95 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Natural Sciences, 1995-96 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Natural Sciences, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Natural Sciences, 1997-98 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Natural Sciences, 1997-98 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Natural Sciences/Philpott, Charles, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Natural Sciences/Review, External, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Natural Sciences/Search, 1997-98 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Shepherd School of Music, 1991-92 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Shepherd School of Music, 1991-93 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Shepherd School of Music, 1992-93 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Shepherd School of Music, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Shepherd School of Music, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Shepherd School of Music, 1996 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Shepherd School of Music, 1997 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Shepherd School of Music, 1997-98 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Shepherd School of Music/ASCAP Contracts and Reports, 1978-80 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Shepherd School of Music/ASCAP Contracts and Reports, 1981-93, 1997-98 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Shepherd School of Music/BMI Contracts and Reports, 1978-96 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Shepherd School of Music/Deferred Gifts-Old Organ and Studio, 1993-94 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Shepherd School of Music/Galas, 1995, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Shepherd School of Music/New Building, 1993-94 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Shepherd School of Music/Pipe Organ, 1988-93 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Shepherd School of Music/Pipe Organ, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Shepherd School of Music/Rice Voice Institute, ca 1989 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Social Sciences, 1989, 1991-92 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Social Sciences, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Social Sciences, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Social Sciences, 1993-95 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Social Sciences, 1994-95 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Social Sciences, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Social Sciences, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Social Sciences, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Social Sciences/Cultural Anthropology, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Social Sciences/Science and Technology Studies, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Social Sciences/Science and Technology Studies, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Development
    - Alumni, 1995-97 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Alumni, 1996-99 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - (Minority) Alumni, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - (Distinguished) Alumni Award and Meritorious Service, 1994-96 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - (Distinguished) Alumni Award and Meritorious Service, 1997-98 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Alumni Events, 1995-97 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Alumni Events, 1996-98 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Assistant Vice President for Public Affairs, 1995-97 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Assistant Vice President for Public Affairs, 1996-98 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Assistant Vice President for Public Affairs, 1997-98 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Associate Vice President for Development and Alumni Affairs, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Associate Vice President for Development and Alumni Affairs, 1997-99 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Associates Events, 1996-2000 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Campaign Leadership, 1998 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - (New) Campaign, 1997-98 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Consular Ball, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Deferred Giving, 1998 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - (Malcolm Gillis) Development Requests, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Endowments, 1996-98 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Estate Planning, 1996-97 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Events and Functions, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Foundations, 1997 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Fund Council, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Fund Council, 1997-98 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Fundraising-Rice, 1995-97 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - (Unrestricted) Gifts, 1997-98 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Homecoming, 1997 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Homecoming, 1998 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - (Office of) Media Relations, 1998-99 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - News and Publications, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - News and Publications, 1997-98 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - News and Publications, 1997-98 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Planning Survey, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Planning Survey, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Rice University Press, 1993-94 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Rice University Press, 1996-97 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Sallyport, 1995-96 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Second Century Committee, 1996-97 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - (Malcolm Gillis') Speechwriter, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Society of Families, 1996-98 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Summit of the Minds, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Summit of the Minds, 1997-98 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Treasurer (Scott Wise), 1998 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - University Relations, 1995-96 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - University Relations, 1996-97 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - University Relations, 1997-98 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Vice President for University Advancement, 1995-96 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Vice President for University Advancement, 1996-97 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Vice President for University Advancement, 1996-97 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Vice President for University Advancement, 1998 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Vice President for University Advancement Search, 1998-99 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - President
    - Affirmative Action/Office of Equal Employment (AA/EEO), 1991-92 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Affirmative Action/Office of Equal Employment, 1987, 1989, 1992-95 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Affirmative Action/Office of Equal Employment, 1994-95 (Box 74, Folder 6)